## Nasreen Muhammad Arif

Email: nasreen\_arif@live.com Contact: 757-957-9144

#### **PROFILE**

Hard working and effective Web Developer with more than 6 years of expertise. Dedicated to achieving demanding project objectives under tight deadlines through successful software design and implementation. Fully proficient in a wide range of development technologies such as .Net, XML and ASP.NET.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **TECHLOGIX - November 2017 - December 2021**

Principal Software Engineer (September 2019 – August 2021) Senior Software Engineer (November 2017 – August 2019)

#### TPS - December 2015 - October 2017

Software Engineer

#### **Generic Solution & Consultancy - September 2014 - December 2015**

Software Engineer (December 2014 – December 2015) Software Internee (September 2014 – November 2014)

#### **EDUCATION**

### Sir Syed University of Engineering & Technology

BS in Computer Engineering

Batch 2011 - 2014 CGPA 3.31

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS

Agile Estimation and Planning certificate

Microsoft Professional HTML5, JavaScript, CSS3 (70-480)

.Net Framework workshop held in SSUET.